var questions = [
  {
    question: 'HTML:',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      'HyperText Markup Letters',
      'HyperText Markup Language',
      'Hyper Transformation Multiple Languages'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'CSS:',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'Cascading Style Sheets',
      'Colouring & Styling Sheets',
      'Cascading Styling Scripts'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'JS:',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      'Johnson Space',
      'Java Semantics',
      'Javascript'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'URL:',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'Uniform Resource Locator',
      'Underworld Reading Lounge',
      'Underline Real Letters'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'HTTP:',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      'HyperTension Transfer Point',
      'HyperText Transfer Protocol',
      'Hyper Train Transfer Point'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'HTTPS:',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      'HyperText Transfer Protocol Version “S”',
      'HyperTension Timing Placement System',
      'Secure HyperText Transfer Protocol'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'SVG:',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'Scalable Vector Graphics',
      'Super Vector Graphics',
      'Scalable Velocity Gaming'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'PNG:',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      'Joint Photographic Experts Group',
      'Portable Network Graphics',
      'Graphics Interchange Format'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'WWW:',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'World Wide Web',
      'Web Wonder Woman',
      'Wide World Web'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'DNS:',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      'Domain Numeral Server',
      'Domain Name Security',
      'Domain Name System'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'TLD:',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      'Tiny Little Domain',
      'Top Last Domain',
      'Top Level Domain'
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'W3C:',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      'World Wide Web Controllers',
      'World Wide Web Consortium',
      'World Web Writers Company'
    ]
  }
];

MultipleChoice(ActivityRunner(), questions);
